Last update: 5/24/2022



Kourosh Ahmadzadeh Ataei

Gmail | in Github | in Linkedin

Personal Data

Address: No.226, Dehkhoda 7 St., Piruzi Blvd., Mashhad, IRAN.

Mobile: +989036928421

Date of birth: December 19, 1996. (25 years)

Place of birth: Ferdows, IRAN

Education

Ferdowsi University of Mashhad (FUM)

Bachelor of Computer Engineering GPA 15.56/20 (3.31 GPA)

• Last 2 years GPA is 16.59 (3.52 GPA)

Relevant Coursework: Data Mining – Algorithm Design - Database - Information Retrieval - Artificial Intelligence – Web Development - Data communication – Multimedia systems - Data Structures

Areas of Interests

Computer Vision, Deep learning, Machine learning, Web development, Rest API, Blockchain, Software engineering, Information Retrieval, Data Mining

Experience

Junior Software Engineer, Co-Founder Al Trader startup (Aran Accelerator)

I am responsible for:

- Develop platform base on python
- Implement telegram bot
- Work with MySQL

Main achievement:

- Acquire team management Teamwork
- Learn and Implement Pattern Designs

- Sysadmin for server side
- Product manager
- Some experiences in product manager
- Participation in Al Project

Mashhad, IRAN

Sep. 2016 - Sep. 2021

Jun. 2022 – Feb. 2022

Last update: 5/24/2022

R&D Developer Jun. 2022 – Feb. 2022

Green Render Startup (Aran Accelerator)

I am responsible for:

Configure render farm - multi-GPUs

Main achievement:

 learn server-side commands and bash script(ubuntu-centos) Work with PostgreSQL

• learn research and development

Swift Developer Intern

Jul. 2020 - Sep. 2020

Part software

I am responsible for:

 Develop IOS applications based on swift and objective-c

Main achievement:

- Learn advance GIT
- Learn swift and IOS development

- Learn swift and XCode
- Do tasks and small project

Selected Projects

Work

Teamus website Feb. 2022 – Present

Developed a web application for team and persons CVs & Resumes

- Based on Django python
- App provides team creation and write their CVs for customers
- Cryptocurrency bot API

Apr. 2022 – Present

Develop an API for cryptocurrency bots

- Based on Django rest framework
- App provides strategies and auto trading for customers with purchase plans

Academic

Mstpd UI
Winter 2020

Data communication, Prof.A. Hosseini, FUM

- Implemented a CLI for Multiple Spanning Tree Protocol Daemon project with configure and installation on Ubuntu based on python
- Optimization on TF-IDF recommender system

Fall 2020

Basics of information retrieval and web search, Prof.F.Ensan, FUM.

 Implemented an optimization on classical TF-IDF algorithm and proposed adaptive weight of position of word algorithm based on TF-IDF

Last update: 5/24/2022

Network security API

Winter 2019

Fundamentals of Secure Computing, Prof.H.Amintoosi, FUM

o Implemented an API with Django Rest API for check ports, show user logs, Token Authentication System, check available website user requests, DDoS prevention

• <u>Charity website</u> Fall 2019

Principles of Database Design, Prof.B.behkamal, FUM

 Implemented a free food distribution web application for charities and restaurant based on PHP and MySQL.

• <u>Air Hockey</u> Winter 2016

Advanced Programming, Prof.A.Nouri Baygi, FUM

JavaFx game application with AI agent

Skills

Languages: (advance)Python, familiar with SQL, Html, CSS, Java, Swift, bash script

Languages: (basic)Java, Solidity, PHP, C

Libraries: NumPy, Pandas, Multithreading, Django, Django REST framework, scrapy, requests

Technologies & Principles: Clean coding & SOLID, OOP, Linux distributions, Git, PyCharm, Google Colab,

XCode, CEH, MVC, Design Patterns, Scrum, fast API, Telegram bot

Languages: English: Upper Intermediate, Persian: Native

About Me

I learned all of my big major of these skills independently although I am **team player** and I willing to **teamwork**. I am **flexible**, **punctual**, **diligent**, **ethical**, **loyal** and **accountable** at work and learn **quickly**. Learning new languages and frameworks enable me to research and develop more and more.